Hello, everyone, friends,
all the videos related to your health protection
are available on our channel, whether you
talk about premium health insurance, standard
health insurance, advance
health insurance, or
accident care policy.
Apart from this, you also get multiple videos related to your claim procedures and phone
filling procedures
on the channel.
We have also given links to all these videos in the description box,
and
you
can watch all these videos by going to the health insurance playlist of the channel. Friends,
people often ask me, like T-shirt, there is an option of
return of premium in life insurance. Is there
any such policy available in health insurance in
which we can get back the premium paid by us?
Friends, the answer to this is
notification. Today, there is no
such policy available in health insurance which
gives you the option of return and premium.
But in today's video, I will
tell you about a product with the
help of which you will be able to claim all those expenses
which you are
not able to claim in your existing health insurance policy. Along with this, you will also know about the benefits of
this product.  With its help,
you will also be able to get the premium return offered in your existing health insurance
policy.
Friends, let's talk about
ICICI Lombard's Cospy Test
product. This product does
not guarantee whether you will get the
premium refund of the existing policy or
not, but it definitely guarantees one thing
that whether you will get the premium refund or not. But
both the situations are going to be different for you. To
know how this is possible, it is
important for us to know
about all the features and benefits of this product.
Friends, on our channel, we
share the latest and useful information with you, with the
help of which you
get help in solving your big problems. And in today's video
also, as a bonus, I will definitely
tell you how with the help of this product,
you can get the premium return of any of your health insurance policies. I
request all of you to watch this video till the
very end with full concentration.
If you like the video, then
definitely like the video, share it and
tell us in the comment box that you liked it.
How did you like the video and friends, if you have
n't subscribed to the channel yet, then first
subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon next to it
so that you keep getting notifications of all our videos from
time to time, so let's start,
in this Dharamveer Singh and your
watching, I am
showing you twice in the loop, it is simple that
in ICICI Lombard's Hospitals product, you have been given two basic years,
in this the first basic news is Hospital
Cash Benefit Jeevan, friends, if you are admitted to the
hospital due to any accident or accident, then
you are given a guaranteed
gift every day, this point can be
anything between ₹500 to ₹10,000,
for what amount your eligibility will be made,
it completely depends on
what option you have chosen while taking the policy,
friends, along with the amount,
while taking the policy, you
also get the option to choose how many days you
want to take out on your birthday, minimum 5
days to maximum 180 days.
You can choose any option. If you have chosen the 30-day
option, then
in case of hospitalization, you are covered for 30 days by a non-
institute insurance company.
Similarly, there is a cutting cover
that is Accidental Hospital Cash Benefit.
Friends, if you are hospitalized due to an accident, then in this, along with the
hospitalization cost-benefit, you are
also given Accidental Hospital Cash Benefit
in additive mode. Friends,
here additive means, for example,
if you have taken a daily outing of Rs. 10,000, then the
company will pay you Rs. 10,000 as hospitalization cost-benefit and then you will get Rs. 10,000 as
Accidental Hospitalization cost-benefit, that is,
Rs. 20,000 here.
You will get Rs. 20,000 here for the number of days of
your hospitalization. Apart from the two basic
covers, 12 extension
covers are also given to you in the policy, in which the most
important cover is ICU. Friends,
intensive care benefit.
In Care Benefit, if
you are admitted in ICU during hospitalization, then along with
its benefit, you are
also given ICU benefit. For example, if
you are hospitalized due to an accident and you are
shifted to ICU
and your hospitalization is for 10 days, then
here
you will get Rs. 10000 as normal hospitalization cash credit,
Rs. 10000 as accidental
hospitalization benefit and
Rs. 10000 as ICU benefit, that is,
you will keep getting ₹3000 for regular 10 days of hospitalization for your family. The
second extension is Cancer
Benefit, friends, if
you are hospitalized due to any serious condition of cancer, then
you will get a guaranteed amount for cancer as well.
Similarly,
you can also avail Heart and Stroke Elements, Heart
Element or Organ Transplantation
Benefit. In these conditions also, the
company will give you a guaranteed amount.
Apart from this, if you
are a regular hosteler for more than 10 days,
then the company gives you a sum of Rs. 10,000.
You can also get information from here for all the day care treatments.
Ambulance expenses are also
covered in this policy.
Apart from this, you get child care benefit and
tanker benefit. If
you are hospitalized for more than three days
and any of your caretakers
travels more than a kilometer to
take care of you, then for that also the
company gives you a guaranteed per day out. You must have liked
all the features and
benefits of this product very much. Friends,
now it is the turn of that bonus tip in which I will
tell you how with the help of this project
you
can get the premium of any of your health insurance policies refined.
Friends, you will understand this with an example.
Suppose you have 30 years of life and
you expect life expectancy and the
advantage of it appears, that is,
for the coming 50 years, you  You purchase a health
insurance policy for yourself, in
which your premium will
be approximately Rs. 7000, if you are taking a basic sum assured of Rs. 10 lakh, but
because this policy is in freezing mode, then
we can assume that you spend Rs. 10,000
on health insurance premium for yourself.
Now, along with this, I
recommend you to purchase ICICI
Lombard's hospital cash product for yourself, for
which again your
premium will be Rs. 6000 or Rs. 6.25, in which
you will get a hospital cash benefit of Rs. 10,000, and
you will get Rs. 10,000 in accidental cash benefit. Along with this,
you can add an extension to it,
ICU Intensive Care Unit benefit of Rs.
10,000, which means that
in case of hospitalization, you will get Rs. 30,000 per
day
premium under this product, but we assume here
that it will
not be possible for you to get all the three benefits always.  You will
also get two, sometimes you will
get three, on an average you should assume that whenever you are
hospitalized you are getting at least 2 benefits, that is you will get a
benefit of Rs 20000, right now here you should
consider that you are super fit and
you are not going to suffer from any disease for the next 20 years,
friends, that is confirmed that
you have never been sick, but
as you move towards old age, the
chances of your illness keep increasing,
but here we consider that
you are eligible for first prize only for 10 days in every 5 years,
friends, so if
you apply for only 10 days in 5 years, then also till
you are 80 years old, you are eligible for 6
days hospitalization and if you are
able to avail the benefit of per day robbers,
then six TDS multiplied by twenty-20
₹1200000 you would have got a return of premium of 15
days
How much premium did you pay in your health insurance policy?
Rs. 10,000 for fears of
Rs. 500 and in the hospital cash policy your
premium is around Rs. 6,000. If you consider this also to be
10,000 patented on increasing mode, then in this
also you paid
Rs. 5 lakh on premium, that is, in both the policies you paid
Rs. 10,000,000 on premium and you get
cash manifest of Rs. 12,00,000 from the policy. So
friends, even if we consider the premium of your policy to be
a little higher, even if we
consider 12,000 instead of 10,000, then also you get
hundred percent return of your premium
and if God forbid,
you go offline for some reason before the age of 50 or
after 50 you are hospitalized for more than 10 days,
then
all the income generated from there will generate an additional income for you through
this product.
I hope you liked the idea friends,
if you are excited  To purchase this product, if
you have any
queries or unsold queries, then without
any hesitation you
can call me on my personal mobile number 9808 or
email me. For my office email
ID I am f8 at gmail.com.
Friends, if you
want to know something about me or my company, then
in the i button above I have given a link to a video clip.
You must watch this clip. And now it's
time for me to sign off. I will meet
you in another video
with some other benefit for you.